costore.com 2017-06-12

# CoreXpand, LLC ("CoreXpand") Privacy Policy

                    CoreXpand, LLC ("CoreXpand") Privacy Policy
At CoreXpand, your privacy is important to us! This Privacy Policy covers how we collect, use,
disclose, transfer, and store your personal information. This privacy statement applies to all
CoreXpand sites and services that display or link to the statement.
1. Collection and Use of Personal Information
When we use the words "personal information," we're referring to information that is personally
associated with just you. You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in
contact with CoreXpand. CoreXpand may combine it with other information to provide and improve
our products and services.
2. What Personal Information is Collected
Here are some examples of the types of personal information CoreXpand may collect and how we
may use it: When you subscribe to CoreXpand’s Services, create an Account ID, register for a web
demonstration, purchase a product, make a donation, or participate in an online survey, we may
collect a variety of information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address,
contact preferences, and credit card information. We may collect and store sensitive information
such as account and purchase information on your behalf as part of the services provided to you. We
collect personal information to deliver or allow access to our products and services. We collect
information about your system as it interacts with us such as your IP address and browser
information. We use common Internet technologies, such as cookies, to manage our Web sites and
services. We frequently collect user feedback and other interactions at our sites.
3. How We Use Your Personal Information
The personal information we collect allows us to keep you posted on CoreXpand’s latest
announcements and software updates. It also helps us to improve our services. If you prefer not to
be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime by following the instructions for unsubscribing. From
time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as
communications about purchases, system maintenance, and changes to our terms, conditions, and
policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with CoreXpand, you may not opt
out of receiving these communications. We may also use personal information for internal purposes
such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve CoreXpand’s products, services, and
customer communications.
4. Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information
We also collect non-personal information or data in a form that does not permit direct association with
any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose non-personal information
including that related to customer activities for any purpose. This information is aggregated and used
to understand which parts of our website, products, and services are of most interest to our
customers. We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information with our partners,
affiliated sites, advertisers, and others. Aggregated data is considered non-personal information for
the purposes of this Privacy Policy. If non-personal information and personal information are
combined, then the combined information will be treated as personal information. CoreXpand, LLC is
the sole owner(s) of all non-personally identifiable information.

5. Cookies and Other Technologies
CoreXpand’s website, online services, interactive applications, email messages, and advertisements
may use “cookies” and other technologies to help us better understand user behavior, tell us which
parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of marketing
and web searches. We treat this information as non-personal information unless required otherwise
by local law.
CoreXpand may also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when
you use our website and services. Our goal in these cases is to make your experience more
convenient and personal. For example, knowing your first name lets us welcome you the next time
you visit the CoreXpand website.
If you want to disable cookies, then follow the help instructions for your particular computer or check
with your provider to find out how to disable cookies. Certain features of the CoreXpand website will
not be available once cookies are disabled.
As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This
information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type and language, Internet service
provider (ISP), referring and exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.
We use this information to learn about user behavior on the site. CoreXpand may use this
information in our marketing and advertising services.
In some of our email messages, we may use a “click-through URL” linked to a CoreXpand website.
When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at
the destination page on our website. This click-through data helps us determine interest in particular
topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked
in this fashion, then please do not click these text or graphic links in the email messages.
Pixel tags enable us to send email messages in a format customers can read, and they tell us
whether mail has been opened. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to
customers.
6. Disclosure to Third Parties
Personal information will not be shared with or sold, rented, licensed, transferred or disclosed to third
parties except as otherwise provided below in Section 7.
7. Disclosure to Others
It may be necessary − by law, legal process, litigation, and/or requests from public and governmental
authorities within or outside your country of residence − for CoreXpand to disclose your personal
information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for purposes of
national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary or
appropriate. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that disclosure is
reasonably necessary to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users.
Additionally, in the event of a reorganization, merger, or sale we may transfer any and all personal

information we collect to the relevant third party.
8. Protection of Personal Information
CoreXpand takes precautions — including administrative, technical, and physical measures — to
safeguard your personal information from loss, misuse, or unauthorized alteration by using industry-
recognized security safeguards. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that
comply with applicable laws and federal standards. Your sensitive information, such as credit card
information, is encrypted when it is transmitted to us. Our employees are trained and required to
safeguard your information. CoreXpand online services use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption
on all web pages where personal information is collected.
9. Integrity and Retention of Personal Information
CoreXpand makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to
date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined
in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.
10. Access to Personal Information
You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to
date by logging in to your account or contacting helpme@coreXpand.com.
11. Privacy Questions
If you have questions or concerns about CoreXpand’s Privacy Policy, please contact us at the
following email address: privacy@coreXpand.com. CoreXpand may update its Privacy Policy from
time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website
along with the updated Privacy Policy.
CoreXpand LLC, One Meca Way, Norcross, GA 30093
Last revised: November 3, 2015
© Copyright 2015 CoreXpand, LLC. All rights reserved.
